[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two countries are connected  by the Simplon Pass?", "correct_answer": "Switzerland and Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["Northern Ireland and Ireland", "Canada and The USA", "Bulgaria and Romania"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Many computer drives have a capacity of a terabit. How many bits are in one terabit?", "correct_answer": "1,000,000,000,000", "incorrect_answers": ["1,000", "10", "8"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elephants express joy by spinning in circles, trumpeting, roaring, screaming, urinating, and flapping their ears. In which of these cases will an elephant not act this way?", "correct_answer": "after the death of an elderly elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["when meeting a friend (elephant or human)", "when playing games", "after the birth of a new baby elephant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who later went on to bigger and better roles, played DEA agent Deets in Point Break.", "correct_answer": "Tom Sizemore", "incorrect_answers": ["John McGinley", "Gary Busey", "Daniel Baldwin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many astrological signs are there in the Chinese zodiac?", "correct_answer": "12", "incorrect_answers": ["24", "4", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The idea of a helicopter was first documented by this man.", "correct_answer": "Leonardo Da Vinci", "incorrect_answers": ["Sikorsky", "Einstein", "Aristotle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which was the second motion picture  to win the Oscar for Best Movie?", "correct_answer": "The Broadway Melody", "incorrect_answers": ["Wings", "All Quiet on the Western Front", "Cimarron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is unique about the reptile called tuatara, which is endemic to New Zealand and is sometimes called living fossils?", "correct_answer": "It is able to hear though it has no ears.", "incorrect_answers": ["It has a well-developed third eye.", "All of these", "It has two rows of teeth in the upper jaw."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these do grizzly bears eat?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Moose", "Berries", "Fish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy movie Norbit, the Latimores open a strip joint.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Arabic name of Mount Etna, the second-largest active volcano in Europe, was Jebel Utlamat. What does this mean in English?", "correct_answer": "Mountain of Fire", "incorrect_answers": ["The Edge of the World", "Home of the Devil", "Breathing Mountain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the movie Appaloosa set?", "correct_answer": "New Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["Arizona", "California", "Texas"]}]